Teachers Union of the City of New York Records 5015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Board of Education Cases, file of Daniman et al, exhibit files, 1952-1955 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Receipt, bills, memo, correspondence, telegrams, cases, news clippings, appeal, verification
- Board of Education, declaration of policy, 1952-1955 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, case, appeal, brief
- Board of Education, declaration of policy, Taylors Decision, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  Case, note, correspondence, appeals, notice of motion
- Board of Education - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Board of Education - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Board of Education - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Board of Education - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Board of Education, Declaration of policy, appeal before Commission of Education, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  News clipping, press releases, cases, appeals, brief, memo, correspondence
- Board of Education, Case of Mildred Flacks, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Board of Education, reinstatements and dismissals, Hash and Maner, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  Cases, correspondence, news clippings, appeal, legal memos
- Board of Education Cases, re: case of charges against Louis Jaffe, 1950-1952 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  Case, simulations
- Board of Education, salary, 1956-1962 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, form letters, statements, press releases, memos, news clippings, post cards, broadside
- Board of Education, suspensions (4), 196l appeal to commissioner, 1960-1963 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  Cases, photocopy, press releases, chronology, statement, memo, telegram, news clipping, correspondence, form letters
- Board of Education cases, teachers hearings, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  cases (5)
- Board of Education of the City of New York, Teachers hearings, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  Cases (8) in single volume
- Board of Education, miscellaneous, 1947-1955 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  News clipping, release, correspondence, form letter invitation
- Board of Higher Education, 1953-1958 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  Report, summary, correspondence, clipping, notes
- Board of Higher Education, re: Case of Seymour A. Copstein, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Board of Higher Education of the City of N.Y., re: Case of Philip S. Foner, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Board of Higher Education, re: case of Walter Scott Neff, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Board of Higher Education, re: Case of Maxwell H. Weisman, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Board of Higher Education, miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Board of Examiners, interpretation of Mitchell Law re requirements of substitute teachers, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  An act, news clippings, correspondence; Brydges-Waters Bill See: Legislation, Salary Campaign Brydges-Waters Bill See: Legislation, Salary Campaign
- Budget, capital, briefs, T.U., City Planning Commission, 1948-1955 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Statements, remarks, report, press release, memo, news clippings, correspondence, form letters, leaflet
- Budgets, capital, 1946-1965 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Analysis and recommendations, briefs, statements
- Building celebration, 1947-1948 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Receipt, post card, correspondence, guest card
- Chores, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, news clippings, memo, list of non-teaching requirements
- Citizen's Committee for Freedom in the Schools, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Form letters, bulletins, release, post cards, pamphlet
- Citizens Union, 1949-1959 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, receipt, list of officers and city committee, directory, program, leaflets
- Civil Eights, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, publication, bulletins, pamphlets, letters
- Clerks, 1947-1952 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  Memo, salaries for school clerks, release, correspondence, form letters, petition
- Collective Bargaining, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  Petition, report, bulletins, leaflets, press releases, speakers list, statement, acts, telegrams, budget, correspondence, form letters, news clippings
- Collective Bargaining, Legal memo, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Photocopies (memo's, telegrams, correspondence), list of incidents
- Collective Bargaining Election and current activities, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  List of eligible teachers, telegram, memo, release, statement of policies and practices, news clippings, correspondence, case, appeals
- Committees, Teachers Union, 1948-1955 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  Notices, memos, programs, note, form letters, correspondence, Publication
- Communism in high schools and youth organizations, Hearings and clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  Hearings, form letter, news clippings, notes; Communists See: Academic Freedom, Communists in the Schools
- Concerts, 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  Contract, correspondence, telegram, news clipping, bulletins, programs, form letters, agreement; Condon-Wadlin Law See: Legislation Condon-Wilson Bill See: Legislation
- Conference, Bill of Rights Conference, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, summary of conference, leaflet, bulletin
- Conference, Teachers Union 7th Annual Education Conference, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Conference, Teachers Union 10th Annual Education Conference, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Conference, Teachers Union llth Annual Education Conference, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Conference, Teachers Union 12th Annual Education Conference, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  Press release, bulletin, correspondence
- Conference, Teachers Union 14th Annual Education Conference, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Press release, excerpts from address, summary
- Conference, Teachers Union 15th Annual Education Conference, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  Bulletins, questionnaire, telegram, press releases, addresses, award, memo, correspondence, form letter speech, news clippings
- Conference, Teachers Union l6th Annual Education Conference, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Conference, Teachers Union 18th Annual Education Conference, Dr. Robert Hutchin's refusal to accept award, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  Correspondence, news clippings, biographical file, reprint
- Congress of American Women, 1947-1950 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  Resolutions, minutes, report, statement, release, memo, receipt, correspondence, form letter, publication
- Congressional Investigations, McCarren Investigation United Public Workers, 1951-1953 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  Statement, publication, bulletins, press releases, fact sheet, news clippings, hearings
- Congressional Investigations, McCarren Committee, Transcripts of Hearings, 1952-1953 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  Form letter, notes from hearings, correspondence
- Congressional Investigations, Senate Internal Security Subcommittee (Jenner), 1953 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  Press releases
- Congressional Investigations, 1948-1951 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  News clippings, weekly, printed reports
- Congressional Investigations, House Committee on Un-American Activities (Velde) Hearings, 1953-1955 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, press release, statement, publication, form letter
- Congressional Investigations (Jenner Committee) Jansen, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  Hearings
- Congressional Investigations, McCarren Commission, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  Press releases, form letters, bulletins
- Congressional Investigations, Senate Subcommittee on constitutional rights (Thomas C. Hennings), 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  Questionnaires, open letter, correspondence, memo, news clipping, publication
- Constitution and by-lavs, 1916-1957 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  proposed constitutions, constitutions, revised constitutions, by-laws, instructions, correspondence
- Contracts, American Radio Institute, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  Contracts
- Contracts, Beachbrook Nursery School, 1950-1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Contracts, Boro Hall Academy, 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Contracts, Boulevard Nursery School, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Contracts, Brooklyn Community School, 1947-1963 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Contracts, Crescent School of Radio & Television, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Contracts, Downtown Community Teachers, 1946-1959 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Contracts, Dramatic Workshop b. Contracts, 1948-1951 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Contracts, Eron Preparatory School, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Contracts, Glen Oaks Nursery School, 1952-1963 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Contracts, Glenwood Nursery School, 1952-1963 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Contracts, Harbor Conservatory, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Contracts, Hebrew Kindergarten and Infants' Home, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Contracts, Hebrew Ladies Day Nursery, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Contracts, Hessian Hills, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Contracts, Inwood Community School, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Contracts, Jewish CoEmunity School, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Contracts, Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order, 1948-1953 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Contracts, Judy Ann Nursery School, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Contracts, Knickerbacker Dental, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Contracts, League School, 1953-1955 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Contracts, Little Red School House, 1948-1961 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Contracts, Melville Radio School, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Contracts, Metropolitan Music School, 1947-1951 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Contracts, neighborhood Music School, 1945-1957 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Contracts, neighborhood Playhouse, 1947-1954 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Contracts, New York Technical Institute, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Contracts, Parkway Music School, 1950-1951 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Contracts, Peter Pan School, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Contracts, Pierce School of Radio & Television, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Contracts, Queens School, 1945-1964 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Contracts, Pickwick Nursery School, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Contracts, Rockwood School, 1946-1951 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Contracts, Rugley School, 1956-1963 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Contracts, School for Jewish Studies, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Contracts, Spuyten Duyuil Infantry, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Contracts, Robert L. Stevenson, 1946-1952 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Contracts, Sunnyside Park Nursery School, 1945-1948 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Contracts, Sunnyside Progressive, 1945-1962 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Contracts, Yeshivak Rabbi Solomon Kluger, 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Contracts, Young Men's and Women's Hebrew Association of East New York, 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Contributions from Teachers Union, 1948-1963 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, form letters, bulletins, receipts telegram, money order, periodical
- Contributions from T.U. to others, 1922-1936 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  Correspondence, form letters
- Contributions to T.U., 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, general, 1920-1935 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  Press releases, correspondence, form letters, report, telegram, news clippings, publications, receipt
- Correspondence, general, 1925-1936 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, press releases, suggested qualifications for U.S. Commissioner of Education
- Correspondence, individual inquiries and answers, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Correspondence with Leonna Abrams, memorial meeting and fund, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, form letters, minutes, program, news clippings
- Correspondence with Ephraim Cross, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with Della Dodd, 1944-1956 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Publication, reprint, photocopy, news clippings
- Correspondence with Dan W. Dodson, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, publication
- Correspondence with Horace W.B. Donegan, 1954-1956 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with W.E.B. DuBois, 1949-1957 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, press release, news clipping
- Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, editorial, publication, press release, news clippings
- Correspondence with Henry Epstein, 1954-1959 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with Martin W. Essex, 1952-1959 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, notes, an appraisal
- Correspondence with Langston Hughes, 1950-1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, photo
- Correspondence with Ella and Eugene Jackson, 1949-1962 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Correspondence with Jacob Javits, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Correspondence with Stanley Isaacs, re: bill concerning organization of city employees, 1951-1961 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  Local law, excerpt from address, routing slip, news clippings, correspondence
- Correspondence with Corliss Lamont, 1952-1961 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  Invitation, news clippings, memo, pamphlet, correspondence
- Correspondence with Abraham Lederman, 1951-1955 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  Press releases, speeches, statement, correspondent
- Correspondence with Abraham Lederman, 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, news clippings, photocopy, releases
- Correspondence with Abraham Lederman, 1961-1963 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  Memo, correspondence
- Correspondence with Abraham Lederman, letters of condolence, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Telegrams, news clippings, correspondence, acknowledgement
- Correspondence with Henry R. Linville, 1920-1936 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, form letter, release, minutes, telegram
- Correspondence with Fred C. Moritt, 1950-1956 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, telegrams, post card, list of committee, release, news release, form letters
- Correspondence with Rose Russell, decisional correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, bulletin, post card, news clipping, telegram
- Correspondence with Rose Russell, reception, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  Testimonials, press release, telegram, correspondence, collection
- Correspondence with Benjamin Schultz, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, news clippings, routing slip, speech
- Correspondence with James Worley, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, case, memos, speech, news clippings, brief Corso Bill See: Legislation Coughlin Bin See: Legislation
- Courses, 1954-1957 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Bulletins, correspondence, reports
- Mary Daniman et al file, Supreme Court of N.Y.S., 1952 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  Transcript of testimony, case, notice of application
- Mary Daniman et al against the Board of Education, Appeal of Teacher, Supreme Court of the State of N., 1952 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  Papers on appeal (3vols)
- Mary Daniman & Shlakman (Slouchower) vs. Port Supreme Court Proceedings, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, cases, notes, jurisdictional statement, news clippings
- Day Care Council, 1950-1956 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Bulletins, correspondence
- Delegate Assembly, general material, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  Bulletins, form letters, announcements
- Delegate Assembly, general material, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Bulletins, form letters, notices, certificates
- Delegate Assembly, General, 1952-1958 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Form letters, bulletins, resolution
- Delegate Assembly, Minutes, 1935-1941 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  Minutes
- Delegate Assembly, Minutes, 1947-1955 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Minutes, correspondence
- Democratic Party, 1948-1956 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, proposals; Democracy in the Schools, Mass Meeting See: Academic Freedom, Committee Mass Meeting
- Discrimination and Segregation, biased textbooks, 1949-1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  News clippings, correspondence, press releases, analysis, bulletin, guide for research
- Discrimination and Segregation, Birmingham, Alabama, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Petitions, press releases, news clippings, correspondence
- Discrimination and Segregation, conference on integration in N.Y.C. Schools, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  News release, correspondence, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, Council Against Intolerance in America, 1949-1954 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Discrimination and Segregation, educational material, books, films, etc., 1949-1955 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Study, book lists, film lists, bulletins, reports
- Discrimination and Segregation, general correspondence, 1955-1963 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  Telegram, correspondence, form letters, news clippings, leaflet, publication, instruction sheet, news release, list of books, statement, post card
- Discrimination and Segregation, general miscellaneous material, 1953-1961 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  Form letter, speech, bus ticket, leaflets, biographical notes, releases, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, General and Schools outside of N.Y.C., 1960-1963 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  Report, bulletins, news clippings, correspondence, press releases
- Discrimination and Segregation, Harlem Committee and Harlem Schools, 1950-1952 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  Brief, bulletins, correspondence, report
- Discrimination and Segregation, Harlem Trade Union Council, 1948-1950 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Discrimination and Segregation, Housing, 1958-1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  News clippings, correspondence, press release, list of supporters
- Discrimination and Segregation, Integration Report, 1957-1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  Statements, telegrams, comment, press releases, testimony, reports, bulletins, cards, post cards
- Discrimination and Segregation, Intergroup Committee on N.Y. Public Schools and T.U., 1959-1961 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  Invitation, correspondence, press releases, statement news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, National Association for Advancement of Colored People, 1947-1955 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, statement, receipts
- Discrimination and Segregation, National Association for Advancement of Colored People, 1956-1960 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  Correspondence, memo
- Discrimination and Segregation, Negro History, 1954-1958 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Discrimination and Segregation, Negro History Week Supplement, 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  Correspondence, form letters, release, article, news clippings, school newspaper
- Discrimination and Segregation, Negro History Week, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  Press release, correspondence, form letters, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, N.Y.C. Schools, Staffing of schools, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  Press releases, correspondence, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, N.Y.C, Public Schools, J. H. S. Brooklyn, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, form letters, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public Schools 2k and 257, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  Post card, memo, correspondence, form letters, news clippings, lists of votes, films, press releases, testimony, notes
- Discrimination and Segregation, Schools in N.Y.C. Negro teachers, 1949-1954 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  Study, press release, resolutions, correspondence, form letters
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public Schools, Negro Teachers, New York, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  Survey, program, study, correspondence, news clippings
- Discrimination and Segregation, public schools, Negro teachers, New York, 1955-1963 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  Program, note bulletins, correspondence, publication, news clippings, study, press release, bus ticket, survey, statement
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  Memo, special census, report, press releases, application for transfer, bulletins, correspondence, form letters
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, N.Y. Board of Education, 1955-1956 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  Reports, budget requirements
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public Schools, N.Y.C. boycotts, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, telegram, telephone message
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, N.Y. correspondence, 1947-1955 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  Bulletins, press release, proposed act, correspondence, form letters
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, N.Y. correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Correspondence, minutes, press release, statement
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, correspondence, non N.Y, 1956-1959 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, congressional record
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools press releases, 1956-1957 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  Press releases, form letter
- Discrimination and Segregation, Public schools, publications (Box 45, Folder 14)
  Form letter, news clippings, correspondence, publications
- Discrimination and Segregation, T.U. intercultural material, 1949-1957 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Press releases, resolutions, correspondence, form letters, surveys, news clippings; Dismissals - Section 903 See: Academic Freedom
- Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1951-1953 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, telegram, pamphlet
- Dues, 1958-1963 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  Form letters, bulletin
- Education (Box 46, Folder 4)
  Paper by Irving Adler, "American Education Today"; Education Bill (Federal) See: Legislation; no date
- Education for democracy, 1938-1940 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  Publications, programs
- Education Conference, 21st Annual Educational Conference, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  Press release, speeches, opening statement, addresses
- Educational Conference, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  Press release, speeches
- Educational Conference, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  Speeches, press release, pamphlet (program)
- Educational Conference, annual, 1937-1963 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, photocopies, publications, news clipping, statement by Kate Smith, cablegram
- Educational Conference, 12th Annual Educational Conference, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, address, form letter
- Educational Conference, 14th Annual Educational Conference, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  Correspondence, address, statement, press release, digest of remarks
- Educational Conferences, 15th Annual Educational Conference, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  Press releases, addresses
- Educational Conferences, l6th Annual Educational Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  Addresses, reprints, press releases, correspondence, form letter
- Educational Conferences, l8th Annual Educational Conference, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  Press releases, speech, address
- Educational Conferences, 19th Annual Educational Conference, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  Address, opening speech, press release, remarks
- Educational Conferences, 20th Annual Educational Conference, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  Press release, speeches, message, opening remarks
- Educational Conferences, 25th Annual Educational Conference, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Program, act, remarks, news clippings, press releases, address, forum, telegrams, correspondence, statement, announcements
- Educational Conferences, 26th Annual Educational Conference, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, biographical, resume, speeches, announcements, programs, publication
- Educational Conferences, 27th Annual Educational Conference, Hotel, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  List, program, correspondence, advertisements, seating arrangement
- Educational Conference, 27th Annual, General correspondence, responses to meetings, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, minutes, invitations, publication, press releases, news clippings, programs, speeches, greetings, photocopies, photos
- Educational Policies Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, press releases, invitations, pamphlets, announcements, list, open letters
- Educational Policies, correspondence, 1918-1936 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Educational Policies, general, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  Speech, correspondence, memo
- Educational Policies, general, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  Minutes, press release, publication, correspondence, news clippings, notes for report
- Educational Policies, retardation (reading), 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, press releases, reading survey summary, news clippings
- Educational Policies, retardation (reading), 1955-1956 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  Program, form letter, correspondence, recommendations press release, minutes, news clippings
- Educational Policy, internal and legislative, 1932-1948 (Box 48, Folder 7)